Guide to the Records of the Office of the Treasurer (Muriel L. Mantel) RG.10
New York University Archives
- Series I: General Administration
  - Supervisor of Property, 1921-1924 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Supervisor of Property, 1925-1931 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Supervisor of Property, 1931-1936 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Supervisor of Property, 1937-1939 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Supervisor of Property, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Supervisor of Property, 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Supervisor of Property, 1946-1952 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Supervisor of Property - Misc. Alternations, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Supervisor of Property, Annual Report, 1931-1934 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Associate Supervisor of Property, 1947-1955 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Property - Building Code Relating to Places of Assembly, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Building Maintenance Report, 1949-1952 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Building Maintenance Report, 1948-1950 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Camp Shanks, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Supervisor of Property, College Housing Program, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Property - Defense Information Re: Material, Equipment and Supplies, 1950-1952 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Property, Supervisor of, James H. Lott, 1945-1949 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Property, Supervisor of, Plant - Five Year Summary Statement, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Military Property Custodian, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Property - Miscellaneous, 1907-1956 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Property - Maps, Educational Properties of New York University, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Property - Mortgages and Leases - 1936, 1939, 1949, 1936-1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Property - Orders: Fire Dept, Tenement House Dept, 1914-1943 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Extraordinary Plant Items, 1919-1920, 1945-1953 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Property - Extraordinary Plant Maintenance Expenditures, 1944-1950 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Property -Extraordinary Plant Maintenance Expenditures, 1944-1951 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Property - Extraordinary Plant Maintenance Expenditures, 1944-1951 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Plant Maintenance and Operations; Plant Personnel Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Property - Plant: Statements for Real Estate and Education, 1946-1950 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Summary of Plant Maintenance and Operations (Work Performed by Outside Contractors), 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Plant Personnel Superintendent, 1934-1948 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Plant Maintenance Payroll, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Postwar Educational Building Maintenance, 1945-1947 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Property - Real Estate, 1927-1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Manager of NYU Real Estate Investment Properties, 1953-1956 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Property and Rents - American Book Company, 1909-1910 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Property, Supervisor of - Reports, 1920-1921 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Property - Water Rates, 1910-1936 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Proposals and Specifications for the Installation of Tabulating Machine Service, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Machine Shop and Forge, 1941-1952 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Westchester Center at White Plains, 1936-1937 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Provost - Budgets, 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Provost - January 1940 - 1952 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Provost - March 1934 - 1939 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Provost Smith -Statement of Feb. 8 to Chancellor Chase, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Provost Smith - Surplus War Property Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Provost - Survey of Income, Expenditures, & Enrollments at NYU, 1916-1939 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Provost Rufus D. Smith - Retirement, 1951-1952 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Public Occasions, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Purchases, Supervisor of, 1916-1924 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - R Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Rationing, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Records Management, 1951-1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Reports of Finance Committee, 1833-1873 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Reports and Statements, 1904-1911 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Reports and Statements, 1911-1915 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Reports and Statements, 1915-1918 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Reports and Statements, 1916-1920 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Reports and Statements, 1920-1921 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Reports and Statements, 1921-1922 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Statements, 1922-1923 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Reports and Statements, 1924-1926 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Reports and Statements, 1926-1930 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Rollins College Clippings, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Social Security, 1940-1949 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU Annual Dinner, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU Annual Dinner, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU Annual Dinner, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU Annual Dinner, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU Annual Dinner, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU Annual Dinner, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Society for the Libraries Bulletins, 1934-1937 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Society for the Libraries Correspondence, 1933-1938 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Society for the Libraries Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU Membership Lists, 1941-1942 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Society for the Libraries: Dockets and Minutes, 1934-1942 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU: Statements, 1934-1942 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Society for the Libraries of NYU: Bulletin, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Special Accountants, 1938-1944 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Special Reports: Library Expenses, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Special Report: Hall of Fame, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Special Reports: Gould Hall, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Special Reports: Bliss Power Plant, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Special Report: NYU Bookstore and Commons Accounts Receivable, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Special Report: Deferred Tuition Loans and Endowed Loans, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Special Report: Institute of International Finance, 1946-1948 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Income, Expense and Appropriations, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Statistics, 1921-1923 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Statistics, 1922-1929 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, 1929-1932 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Statistics, 1933-1937 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Statistics, 1939-1942 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, 1942-1944 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, 1945-1948 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Stoke, Harold, 1955-1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Student Health Insurance, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Student Housing Plans, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Student Services Organization, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Student Leaders, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Summary of Operations, 1913-1921 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Summary of Operations from 1909-10 to 1938-39, inclusive, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Supervisor of Purchases, 1924-1936 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Supervisor of Purchases, 1924-1930 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Syndic, 1910-1919 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Syracuse University Contracts, 1949-1954 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Systems, 1955-1957 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Property Taxes, Bound File, 1936-1956 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Property Taxes, 1907-1935 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Property Taxes, 1935-1943 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Taxes: Section 101 of the Internal Revenue Code, 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Taxes: Section 101 of the Internal Revenue Code, 1946-1951 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Tax Exemption: Statement of John Gerdes to House Ways and Means Committee, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Gerdes Filing No. 900-999, 1954-1960 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Gerdes Filing No. 1000-1029, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Gerdes Filing Medical Center, 1961-1963 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Gerdes Filing No. 1 -899 (incomplete), 1956-1961 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Taxes - Information Required for Tax Exemption by Tax Dept, 1948- (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Taxes - Miller, Cyrus C. Tax Exemption, 1920-1925, 1946-1950 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Taxes Presented to Department of Taxes and Assessments for Exemptions, 1923-1931, 1944-1945 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Taxes - Detailed Lists of Properties and When Applications Were Filed, 1932-1933 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Tax Matters - Mortgaged Property, 1925-1934 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Tax Matters - Mortgaged Property, 1935-1937 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Telegraphs and Fire Alarms, 1926-1950 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Thaler, William, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Thurstone, Kenneth, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Torgersen, Harold - Bookstore Management, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1950-1952 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Turner Construction Company, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Unionization Strike, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - United Airlines Tuition Assistance, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - University Council Finances, 1961-1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Vice Chancellor and Comptroller: Resignation of H. de Wolf Fuller, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Vice Chancellor's Secretary, 1926-1954 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Washington D.C., 1950-1956 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Written Work Standards, 1937-1943 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - World War I, 1917 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - World War I, 1917 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Veteran's Association, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - WNYU, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Series II: Washington Square
  - Arts, School of, 1970, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - 45 Astor Place (Bible House), 1946-1951 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 45 Astor Place (Bible House), 1946-1955 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Cafeteria, 1949-1952 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Students Center, 1952-1954 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - New York University Christian Association, 1946-1953 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Commerce, School of, Building, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Commerce, School of, Building, 1926-1927 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Commerce, School of, Building, 1927 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Consolidated Edison - Main Building, 1915-1922 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - National Defense - Air Raid Defense, 1941-1954 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Dormitories, Proposed, 1924-1939 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - East 20th Street Pipeline Connecting Parts of University Hospital, 1951-1965 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - East 25th Street Property - Installation of 2 Pipelines, 1934-1956, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Club at Washington Square, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Apartment House at Washington Square - #3, 1939, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Fine Arts Building - 17 East 80th Street, 1937-1938 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Foundations and Associations, Proposed Project, 1924-1927, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - General Purpose Building, Proposed, undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Education, School of - 1, 2, & 3 Transfer Files, 1920-1937 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of - Agreement with Chautauqua Institution, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of - Agreements: Little Red School House Child Study Association of America, 1936-1940 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of - Agreements for Field Services, 1948-1956 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Education, School of - Agreement with State Dept of Health Re Public Health Nursing Grant, 1949-1955 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Education, School of - University Atty's File, 1929-1940 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of - Barney Building, Hebrew Technical Institute, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of - Barney Building, Hebrew Technical Institute, 1940-1949, 1966-1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Education, School of - Barney Building, Leases with State of New York, 1941-1948, 1962-1967 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Education, School of - Building, Fire Loss in Basement, 1935-1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Education, School of - Building, 1928-1936 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Education, School of - Building, 1929-1931, 1941-1942 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Education, School of - Camp Lake Sebago (Sup. Of Property), 1930-1957 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of - Center for Human Relations Studies, 1950-1952 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of - Cross Reference: Atty, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of - Defense Training Program, 1941-1945 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Education, School of - Dept. of Music Education, 1923-1924 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Education, School of - Music (formerly Benedict Building), 1924-1934, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of - Jewish Culture Foundation, 1944-1946, 1952-1955 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of - Parsons School of Design, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp, 1924-1929 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp, 1925-1935 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp, 1926-1929 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp, 1935-1937 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corporation Lease, 1935, 1946-1950 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp (1 of 4), 1936-1950 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp (2 of 4), 1925-1936 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp (3 of 4), 1932-1935 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of - Realty Corp (4 of 4), 1929-1932 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Education, School of - Proposed Building Site: Press, Music & Ed, S. Bldg (1 of 2), 1926-1932 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Education, School of - Proposed Building Site: Press, Music & Ed, S. Bldg (2 of 2), 1927-1928 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of - Proposed Building Site…(1 of 2), 1927-1928 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of - Proposed Building Site... (2 of 2), 1925-1927 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Education, School of - Summer Camp, 1941-1961 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Education, School of - United States Committee on Educational Reconstruction, 1943-1945 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Education, School of - Westchester Division of NYU, 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Gallery of Contemporary Art, 1927-1930, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - General Purpose Building, Proposed, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - General Purpose Building, Proposed, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Government Research (1 of 2), 1953-1955 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Government Research (2 of 2), 1953-1955 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Greene Street - Installation of Pipe Lines, 1955-1957 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - 263 Greene Street (Biology-Charipper), 1931-1938 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Greenwich Building Loft 9, 1918-1920 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Greenwich Building Loft 8, 1915-1919 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Greenwich Building - Annex, 1917-1932 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Heating of NYU buildings - Report of John Lowry, Inc., 1941, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 95 Joralemon Street, Brooklyn NY, 1927, 1936-1946 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Judson, 1932-1935 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Judson, 1923-1932 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Judson - Agreements, Lease, Deed, Mortgage - File 1, 1927-1937, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Judson - Agreements, Lease, Deed, Mortgage - File 2, 1925 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Judson (Folder 1 of 2), 1935-1947 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Judson (Folder 2 of 2), 1947-1962 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Judson - Alterations, Annex Special Report, 1939-1947 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Judson Dormitory Building Cross, 1925-1926, 1950-1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Judson Dormitory - Washington Square Student Residence, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Independent Aid, Inc., 1944-1948 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - #30 Lafayette 31 University Place Building, 1949-1953 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Law School Correspondence A-J, 1946-1951 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Law School Correspondence K-Z, 1947-1951 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Law School Fundraising, 1946-1953 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Library/Dormitory, 1924-1963, 1962-1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Library Stack Space (510-20 6th Ave), Lion Ribbon Co. Sublease, 1946-1954 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Machine Shop, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Main/Brown Building (23-29 Washington Place), 1908, 1929-1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Main and Brown Building (23-29 Washington Place), 1929 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Main Building - American Chemical Society Plaque, No. 8 5th Ave, 4-6 Washington Place, 1951-1954 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Main and Brown Building (23-29 Washington Place), 1924-1929 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 23-29 Washington Place (Main-Brown Building), 1923-1924 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Main Building Elevator Installation, 1938-1946 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Maps and Pictures booklets, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Maps of University Buildings, 1924-1956 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square Maps, 1939-1947 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Maps and Pictures - Sailors Snug Harbor and Rhinelander Property, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Museum of Living Art, 1942, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Negotiation between Columbia and NYU (1 of 2), 1947-1948 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Negotiation between Columbia and NYU (2 of 2), 1946-1947 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - New York Life Building, 1930-1932 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Old University Building - Correspondence regarding etchings of, 1926-1948 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Press Building (formerly Celluloid Building), Press Building Sidewalk, Press Building Annex, 1925-1926, 1935-1952 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Property, Assistant Supervisor of Washington Square, 1929-1955 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - NYU Property in the East 20's, 1927-1932 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Power Plant, 1927 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Real Estate - Maps, 1924-1947 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Research Units: Biology, Chemistry, Psychology - Washington Square College, 1926-1949 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Rezoning, 1939-1940, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Sailors' Snug Harbor Property, 1924-1940 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Proposed School of Motion Pictures (1 of 2), 1946 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Proposed School of Motion Pictures (2 of 2), 1946 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Signs in Subway Station, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - South Building, formerly Lies Building, 1924-1947 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - South Building Violation, 1949-1952 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Speyer Block - Campagna Block, 60 Washington Square South (1 of 2), 1928-1942, 1952-1953 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Speyer Block - Campagna Block, 60 Washington Square South (2 of 2), 1926-1930, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Stern School of Business - naming, consolidation, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Student Block Party, 1952-1953 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Students Building, 1947-1949 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Sullivan Street conduit, 1954-1956 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - 245-249 Sullivan Street (University Snack Bar, the Jury Box), 1951-1954 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - 238 Thompson Street - Eviction of Tenants, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - 90 Trinity Place, Proposed Project, 1923-1943 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - 90 Trinity Place, Property, 1919-1951 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 90 Trinity Place - 6th Avenue Elevated Line, 1941-1945 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - University Building Alternations, 1915-1923 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 1 University Place, 1953-1956 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 1 University Place, 1914-1917 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Varick House Spring Street Social Settlement, 1925-1933 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Wall Street Division, 1941-1942 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Wall Street - Property, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Washington Place and West 4th Street - Installation, Maintenance and Use of Pipes underneath and across, 1932, 1943-1967 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Washington Place Closing, 1953-1956 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - 18-24 Washington Place (Washington Square), 1928-1932, 1939-1954 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 18-24 Washington Place (East Building Alterations), 1932, 1946-1952 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 21 Washington Place (1 of 2), 1954-1962 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 21 Washington Place (2 of 2), 1921-1934, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 21-29 Washington Place, 18-24 Washington Place, 1929-1938 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Association (1 of 2), 1945-1957 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Association (2 of 2), 1929-1944 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square Association, 1925-1928 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Building, 1927 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Reconstruction of Washington Square Building, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square Building Alterations (1 of 2), 1921-1922 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square Building Alterations (2 of 2), 1921-1922 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Washington Square Building - William Gregory Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square Building - William Gregory Correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Building - Sprinkler Installation, 1916-1921 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square Building - Sprinkler Alarm, 1920-1924 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Building - Statements and Reports, 1921-1923 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square College (1 of 2), 1947-1956 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square College (2 of 2), 1933-1946 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square College, 1920-1926 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Library, 1928-1935 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square Planning, 1945-1952 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square Property, 1904-1927 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square Property, 1917-1924 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Property, 1925-1935 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square Property, 1927-1929 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Property, 1927-1945 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Property, 1950-1955 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Property, 1947-1955 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square East Proposed Projects, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - No. 1 Washington Square North Lease, 1942-1946 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - No. 1 Washington Square North, 1946-1954 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - No. 2 Washington Square North (1 of 2), 1946-1952 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - No. 2 Washington Square North (2 of 2), 1943-1946 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - No. 2 Washington Square North Lease (15 Washington Mews), 1946 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 5 Washington Square North (Chancellor's Residence), 1940 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - No. 6 Washington Square North, 1950-1955 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square North, 5th Ave, 8th St, University Place block, 1949-1951 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square North, 5th Ave, 8th St, University Place block, 1948-1950 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Nos. 1, 2 and 3 Washington Square North, 1946-1950 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Nos. 1, 2 and 3 Washington Square North - Eviction of tenants and heating project, 1946-1953 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square North -Rhinelander Property, 1948-1951 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square Quarterly - Vice Chancellor and Secretary Office of Student Activities, 1950-1953 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square South Dormitory, Proposed, 1929-1931 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - 50 Washington Square South - Deed from Columbia, 1948-- (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - 51 Washington Square South, Inc., 1929-1936 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - 51 Washington Square South, Inc., 1921-1929 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - 51 Washington Square South for educational purposes, 1935-1936, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 61 Washington Square South (formerly Campgagna property), 1945-1948 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - 61 Washington Square South (formerly Campgagna property) (1 of 2), 1948-1953 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - 76 Washington Square South and Washington Square Faculty Club and YMCA, 1920-1952 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Southeast Project (1 of 2), 1953-1954 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square Southeast Project (2 of 2), 1952-1953 (Box 51, Folder 8)